Files scattered everywhere
no rhyme or reason
video here, subtitles there
it's chaos season
But there's a tool
that's going to change the game
SubX is here
it knows each file by name
AI scanning through the mess,
smart matching nothing less
finding pairs in the digital maze
organizing all your days
SubX, SubX
making sense of all the noise
auto-matching batch processing
it's your choice
from SRT to ASS, VTT to SUB
converting formats
that's the rub
SubX, SubX
timeline sync is crystal clear
No more hunting files
the future's here
Dry-run mode to show you
what it'll do
Preview first, then execute when you're through
Cache remembers what it learned before
Efficiency knocking at your door
Folders full of media files
Process them for miles and miles
Copy, move, rename with grace
Everything falls into place
SubX, SubX,
making sense of all the noise
Auto-matching, batch processing
is your choice,
from SRT to ASS, VTT to SUB
converting formats
that's the rub
SubX, SubX,
timeline sync is crystal clear
No more hunting files
the future's here
Command line power in your hands
Automated workflows, no more manual plans
When subtitles drift and timing's wrong
SubX corrects it, keeps you strong
SubX, SubX, subtitles synchronized
Smart technology that money can't buy
File organization, seamless flow
Let the AI magic show
SubX, SubX, revolution in your CLI
Your media library, now organized
One command, and watch it go
SubX working, head to toe
The subtitle chaos, now controlled
Digital harmony, story told